contus.com 2000-12-15

# Contus.com - Privacy and Security

**[](http://www.truste.org/validate/6305)****CONTUS CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY  
****Contus Corporation (Contus), and its subsidiary companies, respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate- wide Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide.**

**TRUSTe Certification  
**_**This Overall Privacy Statement verifies that Contus is a member of the TRUSTe program and is in compliance with TRUSTe privacy principles. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Web site. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit initiative whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the principles of disclosure and informed consent. Because Contus wants to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed and audited for compliance by TRUSTe. When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe mark, you can expect to be notified of**_ : 

  * **Exactly what personal information may be collected and by what means**
**  
**
  * **Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information**
**  
**
  * **How this information may be used, including who, if anyone, it might be shared with**
**  
**
  * **The consequences, if any, resulting from your refusal to provide personal information**
**  
**
  * **How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company maintains**
**  
**
  * **How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity**
  * **Where and how to ask questions or file complaints**

**If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact the Privacy Policy Administrator David Swank at (419) 868-6090. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe ](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.**

**Contus currently operates the following web sites:  
**

**Contus.com **

| 

**Contus Beaches**  
  
---|---  
  
**Contus Cruise**

| 

**Contus Orlando**  
  
**Contus Golf** | **Contus Alaska**  
**Contus Ski** | **Contus Jr. Olympics**  
**Contus Europe** | **Contus**  
**Contus Off Duty Travel** |    
  
**In addition, Contus owns several other domain names that point to the web sites listed above, and we will, from time to time, add new sites that may, or may not be, listed above. Please note that this policy applies only to sites maintained by Contus or its subsidiaries, and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are "clicking" to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. Furthermore, from time to time, Contus may employ third parties who may collect personal information on behalf of Contus. In such cases, such third parties will be instructed by Contus to comply with the Contus Privacy Policy as set forth herein.**

**What information is collected?  
****Contus only collects personal information from our online visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected from our "Get a Quote" form may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address and information that will be helpful to our agents in providing you with the service you are requesting from us. The "Contact Us" form allows the customer a quicker means of communication with our agents. Customers will be contacted by one of our agents in agreement with the customers' request via email or telephone. Log files are also collected such as IP addresses, ISP and browser type. Log files are collected for internal marketing purposes and are not linked to a user's personal information.**

**What about cookies?**  
**Currently we do not use cookies in our site.**

**What happens to the information provided?  
****When you register on a Contus online site, you will be asked to provide personally identifying information. The information you provide will allow us to alert you to special offers, upgrade travel opportunities, time sensitive information, contests and events of interest. This will be sent via email. Users may opt-out of receiving these communications; see the opt-out section below. None of the information we collect is shared with outside parties. Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs.**

**Opt-out provision**  
**When we first collect information about you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having any communication sent to you other than what is necessary for us to fulfill your travel requirements. (Except to the extent required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.) In addition, if you do not want Contus to send you e-mail or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name removed from our database, you can do so by sending e-mail to[privacy_policy@contus.com](mailto:privacy_policy@contus.com) or by calling (419) 868-6090 or by sending a fax to (419) 868-6099.**

**Safeguarding your personally identifiable information**  
**We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.**

**Review, correction and deletion of information from our files  
****If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by Contus is not correct, or should you wish to have your name removed from our records, please contact us at[privacy_policy@contus.com](mailto:privacy_policy@contus.com) or call (419) 868-6090 or send a fax to (419) 868-6099, and we will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. You may also contact your Contus agent.**

**By using this site, you signify your assent to the Contus Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy. Changes will be posted to the site with prior approval by TRUSTe. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Contus will require your consent if these changes allow the use of personal information in a manner that differs from what was stated at the time the information was originally collected.**
